by RentAnAdviser.com
Secrets whispered through
a veil of lies
When did I become this
person you despise?
Open my eyes
You've been in disguise
The door is closing
You're on the outside now
It's curtain call
After everything I did for you
This is what you choose
to put me through?
What happened to the
concept of loyalty?
I guess there really
is no more honesty!
Open my eyes
You've been in disguise
The door is closing
You're on the outside now
It's curtain
It's curtain call
Deceiver, deceiver
My head still spinning
from your Judas kiss
Deceiver, deceiver
Not one thing about you I will miss
You put on a great act,
I'll give you that
Go on and take a bow
you despicable rat
Accept the applause,
you king of whores
This is your grand finale
Deceiver, deceiver
My head still spinning
from your Judas kiss
Imposter, I see you
Thou beest slain, tyrant,
show thy face!
Open my eyes
You've been in disguise
The door is closing
You're on the outside now
It's curtain call
Deceiver, deceiver
I see... you!
by RentAnAdviser.com