When I was born
the seed was sown.
I will not obey, my life is my own.
Battle those
who which to enslave me
Expose the lies
that enrage me
I don't believe in Heaven, I don't be believe in Hell
Never joined the herd
could not adjust well
slave, master,
it's not for me
I chose my own path
Set myself free.
I
I go my own way
Swim against the stream (forever)
I will fight the powers that be
I
I go my own way
I swim against the stream(forever)
I will fight the powers that be
The eagle flies alone
Riches in the system
But it takes the norm
This world is full of lies and deceit
I ask my own betrayal
Cut so deep
suffered defeat
Only to rise agains
I
I go my own way
I swim against the stream(forever)
I will fight the powers that be
I
I go my own way
I swim against the stream(forever)
I will fight the powers that be
The eagle flies alone
ALONE!!
I
I go my own way
I swim against the stream (forever)
I will fight the powers that be
I
I go my own way
I swim against the stream(forever)
I will fight the powers that be
The eagle flies alone