Tell me was it all worth it,
to watch your kingdom grow?
1 - OK
Sunk this low
2 - OK
Now we're gone, left without a trace
3 - OK
But we took something
they cannot replace
4 - OK
A match made in heaven,
paved the road to hell
5 - OK
We've been down this path before
6 - OK
Cold blooded retribution,
So fuck your revolution
7 - OK
You chew up peace and
spit it out as war
8 - OK
You've been feeding the wolf
that's waiting at the door
9 - OK
You are rotten to the core
10 - OK
Found your fingerprints
all over the trigger
11 - OK
If you're looking for tyrants,
take a look in the mirror
12 - OK
You knew all along, that
the cancer would spread
13 - OK
Don't be surprised to find
a price on your head,
sorry son, but we destroyed your home
14 - OK
We murdered your family,
now you're on your own
15 - OK
Collateral damage, face
down in the sand
16 - OK
Watch the dominoes fall, it's
all just part of the plan
17 - OK
A match made in heaven,
paved the road to hell
18 - OK
We've been down this path before,
Cold blooded retribution,
So fuck your revolution
19 - OK
A match made in heaven,
Paved the road to hell,
We've been down this path before
20 - OK
And every execution, the
price of your collusion
21 - OK
along, that the cancer would spread
22 - OK
So don't be surprised to find
a price on your head
23 - OK
Tell me was it all worth it,
to watch your kingdom grow?
All the anchors in the ocean
haven't sunk this low
24 - OK
are rotten to the core,
You are rotten to the core,
You are rotten to the core