by RentAnAdviser.com
Take them all back
I'm not too sure what I'm
supposed to do with this
These hands, this mind,
this instability
From a cage I created, to
a hell that heaven made
Can't let go of the hatred, 'cause
I love the way it tastes
Take them all back
I wouldn't take back a moment
Not one miserable moment
I'll give it all, 'til there's nothing
I'd walk into the fire
Into the fire
I've come to terms with the
fact I'll never change
And that's just fine, I find
solace in the pain
I don't mind the darkness,
it's easy on the eyes
I'm praying for something
to make me feel alive
I wouldn't take back a moment
Not one miserable moment
I'll give it all, 'til there's nothing
I'd walk into the fire
Into the fire
I'm a paranoid, sycophant,
masochistic dilettante
Narcissistic elephant in the room
I'm the end of the world,
thinning the herd
The all around outta my
mind, fucking absurd
I am gone, I am gone
I wouldn't take back a moment
I'd walk into the fire
Into the fire
Fire
Take them all back
by RentAnAdviser.com