By RentAnAdviser.com
Oh my God.
If only he knew,
If only he knew about the world without
the bullshit and the lies,
We could've saved him.
They could've saved me.
But instead I'm here drowning
in my own fucking mind,
And I'll be damned if you're
the death of me.
Blood and ink stain the walls.
Silently with bloodied
knuckles, I carry on
Hoping it's not too wrong.
You said the nights were far too long.
'Honey, it's just the start of it.'
Oh my God.
If only he knew.
If only he knew!
Just stand up and scream.
The tainted clock is counting down.
(Faster and fast!)
You gave in to me.
Would you say the nights
are far too long now?
(Faster, and faster and fast!)
(My God!)
Oh my God!
Oh my fucking God!
The tears that stain my cheek
make me look weak!
I wear them proudly!
I wear them proud!
Just stand up and scream.
The tainted clock is counting down.
(Faster and fast!)
You gave in to me.
Would you say the nights
are far too long now?
(Faster, and faster and fast!)
Your knife,
My back!
My gun,
Your head!
Your knife,
My back!
My gun,
Your head!
You need a doctor baby,
You scared?
You scared,
Yeah!
You need a doctor baby,
You scared?
You need a doctor baby!
By RentAnAdviser.com