by RentAnAdviser.com
Close the curtains, cash me in
Gather photographs of
the Devil you let in
Digging deep inside my soul
I don't know, I don't know
Where to turn
Everywhere I look these vultures burn
The life right outta me
Do I run or lay down and die?
Is it time to close my eyes?
Keep me numb, I'll follow direction
A pawn to pass around and
be bled until I'm dry
It's hard to see what's underneath
Is it me? Is it me?
Where do I turn?
Everywhere I look these vultures burn
The life right outta me
Do I run or lay down and die?
Is it time to close my eyes?
For so long all I've known,
all I've seen's
Green lights. Fuck your greed,
all I need's somewhere
To catch my breath, rest my
head and ease my mind
I've been holding on
But my grip ain't what it used to be
I'm much older, I'm bitter,
I'm jaded, I'm lost
Can somebody give me a sign?
Where do I turn?
Everywhere I look these vultures burn
The life right outta me
Do I run or lay down and die?
Is it time to close my eyes?
Where do I turn?
Everywhere I look these vultures burn
The life right outta me
Do I run or lay down and die?
Is it time to close my eyes?
by RentAnAdviser.com