By RentAnAdviser.com
One, two, three, four (all
the things that she said,
was it all in my head?)
Come on, baby
Keep it down
Honey, hush your lips
Clothes trailing
From the backdoor
To the bedroom
And I don't even know your name
Give me all you've got
Make this night worth my time
Make this worth my time (oh)
What I would give to live
this night again
I knew when I first saw you
You'd fuck like a whore
I can hear you screaming
for more (yeah)
Your thighs were made
for cheeks to graze
My lips, your poison
They bring you to your knees
Your thighs were made
for cheeks to graze
My lips, your poison
They bring you to your knees
Ah, come on
Girl, get down
It's almost over
Take it all the way
Oh
You stupid fucking whore
And after all of all my dreaming
being only you
You're standing there, baby, oh
The things that I could do
Back to the wall with
a drink in my hand
Back it up, baby, ride, ride, ride
One step too late
And I never told you
That I can't take
Another disappointment
Breathing and grasping all leads
to another messy ending
Ten inch
With your back against the wall
With your face buried in the pillow
I see you cold
I feel you heartless
Bitch
You stupid fucking bitch
Fucking bitch
By RentAnAdviser.com