by RentAnAdviser.com
Yo, fuck what you heard, this Attila
back with that heavy shit
I am the Devil
If you're down with the
Devil say "Hell yeah"
Hell yeah
Learn to forget it and look
ahead in the future again
If you're down with the
Devil say "Hell yeah"
Hell yeah
Sinning is winning, let's start
it from the beginning again
Don't forget the reason we're all
here: to live our best life
Don't judge me based on your collusion,
it's just a god-damn lie
When will you see through the bullshit,
opinions equal shit
Let me see your three six
Go
If you feel it, fucking sing it
I'm burning down your church
like six six six
Can you smell the fire burning
like it's six six six?
Yah
If you're down with the
Devil say "Hell yeah"
Hell yeah
Learn to forget it and look
ahead in the future again
If you're down with the
Devil say "Hell yeah"
Hell yeah
Sinning is winning, let's start
it from the beginning again
I'm burning down your church
like six six six
Can you smell the fire burning
like it's six six six?
I'm burning down your church
like six six six
Can you smell the fire burning
like it's six six six?
I am the Devil
Will you live a life of indulgence?
Will you sit back and watch
on the sidelines?
Everything is nothing but an illusion
Stop judging us based
on your guidelines
Keep your opinions to yourself, bitch
Go live your life, I'll
live with my sins
Take a step back and see your delusion
You live a life based on
lies and confusion
If you feel it, let me hear it
I'm burning down your church
like six six six
Can you smell the fire burning
like it's six six six?
I'm burning down your church
like six six six
Can you smell the fire burning
like it's six six six?
If you're down with the
Devil say "Hell yeah"
Hell yeah
by RentAnAdviser.com