One, two, three, four.
You know what you are?
1 - OK
A pizza poser, fuck you
2 - OK
I've never seen you eat a slice.
To you it's just a trend, pizza is my life
3 - OK
Pizza is my life
4 - OK
Thin crust deep dish double pepperoni.
Elios stuffed crust, no anchovies.
Pizza Rolls, Bagel Bites, cheesy crust is what I like.
Put it in the oven, we can order delivery.
I don't care, I'm not very picky.
Warm and delicious, spicy, sticky.
Cut in to eight squares or triangles,
All I really want is pizza in me
5 - OK
Pizza is the greatest food in earth
6 - OK
Well, shit
7 - OK
I got drunk with Papa John.
He snorted cocaine with his apron on
8 - OK
He got too fucked up for delivery
It was over thirty minutes so my pizza was free. Oh!
9 - OK
P I Z Z A
10 - OK
11 - OK
Fucking pineapple
12 - OK
Pineapple doesn't belong on pizza.
You fucking piece of shit
13 - OK
Why would you do this to me?
14 - OK
I'm gonna peel your eyes out of your fucking skull
15 - OK
I will extract your blood, use it as pizza sauce