Fly!
1 - OK
She starts her new diet of liquor and dick
2 - OK
Just like Hollywood but laced in sick
3 - OK
The sun goes down, and so does she
4 - OK
5 - OK
Sold out the love that she had, with a cut of the throat
6 - OK
Drinks all round on her, before she strolls to the moat
The sun goes down, and so does she
7 - OK
8 - OK
Count!
9 - OK
Count your fucking blessings
10 - OK
Come on!
11 - OK
Count your blessings, 'cause I'm counting every lie
12 - OK
Count your blessings, 'cause I'm counting every lie, counting every lie
13 - OK
Christ! I'm asking you for just one thing
14 - OK
I'm asking you for just one thing
15 - OK
Eradicate, this disease
16 - OK
Close your eyes
17 - OK
Pray for plagues,
Oh Lord cleanse this earth and bring upon our doomsday
Oh! Close your eyes
18 - OK
Pray for pleagues
19 - OK
Cleanse this earth and bring doomsday
20 - OK
She starts her new diet of liquor and dick
21 - OK
Just like Hollywood but laced in sick.
The sun goes down and so does she
22 - OK
The sun goes down and so does she.
So clap your hands, to the sound of every firstborn dying now,
watch the rivers flow with blood, death we'll stand where life once stood
23 - OK
So clap your hands, to the sound of every firstborn dying now,
watch the rivers turn to blood, death we'll stand were life once stood.
watch these rivers turn to blood, death we'll stand were life once stood
24 - OK
Close your eyes, pray for plagues
25 - OK
Cleanse this earth