By RentAnAdviser.com
For the love of god, will
you bite your tongue
Before we make you swallow it
It's moments like this where
silence is golden
(And then you speak)
No one wants to hear you
No one wants to see you
So desperate and pathetic
I'm begging you to spare me
The pleasure of your company
(When did the diamonds
leave your bones?)
I'm burning down every bridge we make
I'll watch you choke on
the hearts you break
I'm leaving out every word you said
Go to hell for heaven's sake
I'm burning down every bridge we make
I'll watch you choke on
the hearts you break
I'm leaving out every word you said
Go to hell for heaven's sake
(Go to hell for heaven's sake)
No one wants to hear you
(save your breath)
No one wants to see you
So desperate and pathetic
You think that no one sees this
I think it's time you knew the truth
I'm burning down every bridge we make
I'll watch you choke on
the hearts you break
I'm leaving out every word you said
Go to hell for heaven's sake
I'm burning down every bridge we make
I'll watch you choke on
the hearts you break
I'm leaving out every word you said
Go to hell for heaven's sake
When did the diamonds leave your bones
Leave your bones
You're not a shepherd,
you're just a sheep
I'll cut my depths of
everyone you meet
Your own flesh with no bones
Feed them to the sharks
And throw them to the walls
I'm burning down every bridge we make
I'll watch you choke on
the hearts you break
I'm leaving out every word you said
Go to hell for heaven's sake
I'm burning down every bridge we make
I'll watch you choke on
the hearts you break
I'm leaving out every word you said
Go to hell for heaven's sake
Go to to hell for heaven's sake
By RentAnAdviser.com