By RentAnAdviser.com
Helpless, my eyes are bleeding
from the fear that's inside,
You sealed your demise when
you took what was mine
Don't try and stop me from
avenging this world,
No voice to be heard
Waking the Demon,
Where'd ya run to
Walking in shadows,
Watch the blood flow
There's not much longer so
don't try and fight,
Your body's weakening
so walk to the light
All those painful times
so alone so ashamed,
I'm not coming back there's
nothing to gain
Caution, there's just no limits
to the boundaries you push,
I've warned you but still you
just fuck with my mind
There's no escape from this
rage that I feel,
Nothing is real
Waking the Demon,
Where'd ya run to
Walking in shadows,
Watch the blood flow
There's not much longer so
don't try and fight,
Your body's weakening
so walk to the light
All those painful times
so alone so ashamed,
I'm not coming back there's
nothing to gain
Breath for me,
Don't wake me from this slumber
Stay with me,
Possession taking over
Breath for me,
Don't wake me from this slumber
Stay with me,
Possession taking over
Breath for me,
Don't wake me from this slumber
Stay with me,
Possession taking over
Breath for me,
Don't wake me from this slumber
Stay with me,
Possession taking over
Waking the Demon
By RentAnAdviser.com