Experimental pathogens, a devil's design
1 - OK
The dark side of science breeds a weapon of war
2 - OK
Contagious killing and internal distress
3 - OK
Homicide or suicide will be the cause of death
4 - OK
Internal organs altered by the disease
5 - OK
Your brain disabled by the constant pain
6 - OK
Erratic actions lead my thoughts to the blade
7 - OK
I've lost control, I've lost control.
Beg for your life, you won't escape the knife
8 - OK
Your fate was sealed today
9 - OK
Disease has spread, you pray for death
10 - OK
Evisceration plague
11 - OK
Stabbing compulsion overwhelms my mind
12 - OK
Terrorized screaming follows the thrust of my knife
13 - OK
I wrench the blade from the chest to the crotch
14 - OK
Organs and entrails fall to the ground.
Beg for your life, you won't escape the knife
15 - OK
Your fate was sealed today
16 - OK
Disease has spread, you pray for death.
Evisceration plague
17 - OK
Driven to kill, this is not my will
18 - OK
I am compelled to slay
19 - OK
Invisible foe takes control.
Evisceration plague
20 - OK
Unable to be seen but with visible effect.
Virulent disease causing outbreaks of violence.
They tear themselves apart, offal covers the ground
21 - OK
Viscera torn forcefully from the abdomen.
Intestines slick with blood cannot escape my grip.
Surgical incisions give way to frenzied carving.
Delirium has taken hold, disembowelment is complete
Horror grips my mind, my entrails are in my hands,
my entrails are in my hands,
my entrails are in my hands
22 - OK
Plague leads to death.
Plague leads to death
23 - OK
Disease will spread and cover the world
24 - OK
Mass insanity, the end of our time.
Scavengers will eat the remains of man.
Our extinction was by our design.
Beg for your life, you won't escape the knife.
Your fate was sealed today
25 - OK
Disease has spread, you pray for death.
Evisceration plague
26 - OK
Driven to kill, this is not my will.
I am compelled to slay.
Invisible foe takes control.
Evisceration plague