by RentAnAdviser.com
Before the wall is caved, our temple
Pressed upon the face of england
we were suffering
To nothing less than the matter
of a socialist test raid
Dagger in the peace wicked
time disdained
Then empires saw much more to gain
The crown discounts are lost
Like a knot, count the cost
These numbers felt like water
The death and dying on
route to slaughter
Valen-times we've spined entwined
I am sorry that i left you here
In time i will find, the puppet
from the other side
So keep a candle burning in your
heart that is my shrine
Spilling tears fill a laboratory
Love's not responding beyond the pyre
The portent is promissory
Prevalence of this Seance in obeisance
To the spirits before Death's victory
The crown discounts are lost
Like a knot, count the cost
These numbers felt like water
The death and dying on
route to slaughter
Valen-times we've spined entwined
I am sorry that i left you here
In time i will find, the puppet
from the other side
So please accept my kisses through
the whispers of the winter morn'
I suffer alone
So far from home watching
you from a distance
A shadow persistent to mourn
No time to atone, you vow a renown
Beautifully craven you cut the black
raven who's tower has flown
Spilling tears fill a laboratory
Love's not responding beyond the pyre
The portent is promissory
Prevalence of this Seance in obeisance
To the spirits before Death's victory
Winter seems far colder
Without you by my shoulder
now this year
by RentAnAdviser.com