by RentAnAdviser.com
Ravaged are the heavens
Seven angels are deployed
The seals delivered
To return us to the void
And waiting on the cusp
of many dusks of man
He watches as the masses
seek a fake salvation
As He breeds annihilation
Now death is law
Venom dripping from the
mouth of madness
Incites the rites of war
Prepare the heights of Empire
for the agonising fall
The beast is rising
Enwreathed in flame
The soundtrack bleeds insanity
His theme, the screaming End Of Days
Come
Crawling King Chaos, come
Sing his name in rapture, wormwood
bitter, spat in tongues
Of ancient Pandemonia for the
ghosts all shall become
Returning to the churning
of primordial seas
The Order Of Disorder restored
through tribulation
Through this bred annihilation
The whole world is his church now
A seismic paradigm shift to chaos
Apophis
Reach dark office
Seize the Goddess
Apophis
Reach dark office
Seize the Goddess
Apophis
Reach dark office
Be the prophet's propaganda
The beast is rising
A cancer at the core
Of everything accelerating
To Death's apathetic maw
The beast is rising
Underlit by gore
Stone tablets crack, humanity
Is doomed to looming horror score
Scatter brittle insects, fate is heard
In the necrotic birth
Of the terminus plague
Satan has fallen
Midst dark waters of the Earth
Come
Crawling King Chaos, come
Mountains heave great murmurs
Fires raze the forests black
As billions flee the horsemen
Creation, wounded, staggers back
To expire in the mire, wiped
from all of time
It will be eternally that
we never existed
By this bred annihilation
Apophis
Reach dark office
Seize the Goddess
Apophis
Reach dark office
Seize the Goddess
Apophis
Reach dark office
Be the prophet's propaganda
The beast has risen
Behind the sun
The least unleashed is Armageddon
For everything and everyone
The beast has risen
Tearing wide the door
For our burning footprint
On a cindered world, sinning no more
A cindered world, sinning no more
by RentAnAdviser.com