by RentAnAdviser.com
Incite a riot, put yourself
in a trance
You rotate the frame in
a world you rely on
A scar, a line has been
drawn in the sand
Behold the life, the boundaries
fools will crush
The greatest miracle
Is burning to the ground
Onto the next stage of the plan
Mourn the witness of the wind
A handful of thunder
Will rise one last time
There's fire in the sky
You're in the Amazon
The greatest miracle
Is burning to the ground
Godly Amazonia
Bloody Amazonia
Mighty Amazonia
Killing Amazonia
Godly Amazonia
Bloody Amazonia
Mighty Amazonia
Killing Amazonia
Godly Amazonia
Bloody Amazonia
Burn
The land
Learn
The end
Burn
Another gold mine is unveiled
The source of our sorrow
Learn
Embedded in these walls of green
Is the curse that we follow
There's fire in the sky
You're in the Amazon
The greatest miracle
Is burning to the ground
by RentAnAdviser.com