by RentAnAdviser.com
Say something about awakening
The rebellion you felt before
Wake, change your course
Laws will follow
Restart, reactivate the core
Rise
Yeah, you come out
You're awake now
Put your fist in the air
You were hiding
Now you throw yourself
Into the storm
Stand
Gather your strength, raise your eyes
Fear not the demons you're up against
Now that you dove down
Found the bottom begging for air
How sad, how long it takes
us to rise and fight
Yeah, you come out
You're awake now
Put your fist in the air
You were hiding
Now you throw yourself
Into the storm
Flames
Dancing in the open
You step into the light
Now that you dove down
Found the bottom begging for air
How sad, how long it takes
us to rise and fight
Yeah, you come out
You're awake now
Put your fist in the air
You were hiding
Now you throw yourself
Into the storm
Storm
by RentAnAdviser.com