by RentAnAdviser.com
Swallow your freedom
Swallow your smile
Swallow your sanity that crawls
and itching inside
We got the cure
We got your fate
We got everything you want so you
don’t have to think again
From botanicals to synthetic drugs,
pharmaceutical industry is born
It is not to cure
It’s about to control
Your money, your health
They want to own it all
You’re the chemical whore
They make you beg on
your knees for more
A chemical whore
Steals your life, steals your mind,
whatever is left of your soul
We’ll make you addicted
Our little bitch
We love your money much more
than your pity health
With our expensive pills
We control your fear, we disconnect
you and tell you what to feel
From botanicals to synthetic drugs,
pharmaceutical industry is born
It is not to cure
It’s to control
Your money, your health
They want to own it all
You’re the chemical whore
They make you beg on
your knees for more
A chemical whore
Steals your life, steals your mind,
whatever is left of your soul
Tranquillized mind
To make sure you won’t
make trouble or fight
Remote controlled drugs
You can’t tell right
from wrong or lies
You’re the chemical whore
They make you beg on
your knees for more
A chemical whore
Steals your life, steals your mind,
whatever is left of your soul
by RentAnAdviser.com