The serpent knows
When the curtain falls
With denials blindfold
He greets another day
Don't believe the mask
It adapts to any lie
A perfect ten
When reality caves in
Don't tell me
Tell my ghost
'Cause I blame him for all
I don't want to know
I found secrets about life's undertow
Life's wrapped in a riddle
Easier said than done
Hate to play the victim
Rather run and hide
Don't believe the mask
It adapts to any lie
A perfect ten
When reality caves in
Don't tell me
Tell my ghost
'Cause I blame him for all
I don't want to know
I found secrets about life's undertow
Let them take me far away
Crawl back in place
It's easier to cope behind the curtain
Wipe the worries away
No thought about the consequence
Don't believe the mask
It adapts to any lie
A perfect ten
When reality caves in
Don't tell me
Tell my ghost
'Cause I blame him for all
I don't want to know
I found secrets about life's undertow
Let them take me far away