Stop!
1 - OK
Go!
2 - OK
Go on!
3 - OK
My wish would be
4 - OK
To see this sun shining
5 - OK
To hear these birds singing
6 - OK
Children laughing, hearts recovering
7 - OK
My dream has always been
8 - OK
Life has always seemed
9 - OK
To be an amusement park
10 - OK
Rather colourful than dark.
I wanted a loser to win
11 - OK
The thin never starving
12 - OK
The full not keeping it down
13 - OK
And needing nothing from no one
14 - OK
I wanted the poor to live in abundance
15 - OK
I wanted the rich to have someone
16 - OK
Except for himself
17 - OK
To love and take care of.
I wanted a loser to win
18 - OK
The thin never starving
19 - OK
The full not keeping it down and needing nothing from now on
20 - OK
Fires burning all around us
21 - OK
And all we feel is cold
22 - OK
I want a neighbour not a hater
23 - OK
And a head to go round
24 - OK
From white white snow
25 - OK
But what to do now?
26 - OK
Wish I could catch god by the beard
27 - OK
And drag him to the dirty streets
28 - OK
To show him what was going on
29 - OK
The kind of curse we've waged upon
30 - OK
We're half way through to freedom
31 - OK
The path is treacherous
32  - OK
The best way to make a kettle boil
33 - OK
Is to turn your back on this
34 - OK
You've stranded me with no decree
35 - OK
No lessons given, only learned
36 - OK
Cold blood is coursing
through my veins
37 - OK
Cause ice will never burn
38 - OK
What is happiness?
39 - OK
What is inner peace?
40 - OK
What do we have to do
41 - OK
To get a piece of you?