Haunted by the nature's fury
as the legend reads
1 - OK
You set off to search for a new
land as your master pleads
2 - OK
Wood and nails, they create
the masterpiece
3 - OK
The ark is gliding upon
the flooded surface
4 - OK
The wind is welcoming and
pushing it forward
5 - OK
The ark is on the tide, tide is high
6 - OK
Keep it safe and sound,
what you have inside
7 - OK
What is meant to be, let
it be (Let it be)
8 - OK
A blessing is a shield
in your time of need
9 - OK
The ark is gliding upon the ocean
10 - OK
A placid giant on a mission.
The wholesome deed is transition
11 - OK
Of living creatures to the other side
12 - OK
To find a mountain the giant glides
13 - OK
Noah!
14 - OK
Something went wrong, huh?
15 - OK
I can hear the animals moaning
16 - OK
Dogs are howling in their roomless cage
17 - OK
Why are you standing frozen with fear?
18 - OK
Staying on the boat for weeks
19 - OK
Where the sea and the air are still
20 - OK
You sent a dove to find a seed
21 - OK
You sent a dove but it will not return
22 - OK
What is meant to be, let it be
23 - OK
Keep it safe and sound,
what you have inside
24 - OK
The ark is imprisoned by the ocean
25 - OK
A placid giant failed the mission
26 - OK
Horizon bends over hiding dryland
27 - OK
The giant surrenders the
quest for a mountain
28 - OK
Skies are falling, Noah!
29 - OK
This woe just can't be gone
30 - OK
The horizon is bending over
31 - OK
And now it's upside down