This autumn feels like funeral to me
2 - OK
And not for what has passed
3 - OK
But for what shall last
4 - OK
Exhausted nature is so
tragic and suicidal
5 - OK
Oh how spectacular she is
when she kills herself
6 - OK
Death throes are slowly
crawling to her toes, as the last leaf is falling off her head
7 - OK
I'm here with her undressed
8 - OK
With a few petals on my breasts
9 - OK
We shared opiates and let the
landscapes do the same
10 - OK
I love your warmth but yet prefer
to sleep in cold alone. We fixed our eyes up to the sky
11 - OK
To see a flight send us farewell
12 - OK
Goodbye
13 - OK
May we see each other next time.
So please, come back to celebrate
this festival of life then as now fly
14 - OK
Today you reached the
point of no return. Now cry and then die
15 - OK
Tomorrow I will meet you with
your cells restored
16 - OK
Annual tradition of mass destruction
17 - OK
In the name of total reconstruction
18 - OK
My biggest source of confusion
19 - OK
The reason of decay and disillusion
20 - OK
Under permanent ice
21 - OK
We found a breathless paradise
22 - OK
No, we're not dead
23 - OK
24 - OK
Just enjoying coma
25 - OK
From the ashes of my roots
26 - OK
The new me will rise to live again
27 - OK
This is poetry of youth
28 - OK
This is poetry of me and you
29 - OK
From the ashes of my roots
30 - OK
The new me will rise to live again
31 - OK
This is poetry of youth
32 - OK
This is poetry of me and you