by RentAnAdviser.com
I keep on losing the keys
From reality
And now I'm passing on the wheel
To insanity.
In a secluded corner
Waiting for my time to come
Waiting for the bedlam
To be pacified
I am climbing hand over fist
And I scratch concrete
Shine in the end My mistake
It's not there
The air is terribly heavy here
It settles inside
And I suffer burn after burn
From the dark. Burn
In a pit of consciousness
Squeal is bleeding
So I feel there was someone else
Before me.
Eyes are changing colors
A stranger knocks on my mind
I became a foreigner
To myself!
Myself!
Stillness stuns. Wish I'd run
Creeped away to the light
In my head someone else
Setting snares
For my soul
In the darkest place
What was once named consciousness
I'm a miniature
I'm a sketch forfeiting outlines
Irrelevant entity to sanity
A hive for nonsense
For multiple selves
Resonating, but never compromising
Stillness stuns. Wish I'd run
Creeped away to the light
In my head someone else
Setting snares
For my soul
by RentAnAdviser.com