by RentAnAdviser.com
The beginning of all beginnings
The era of nonexistence
When the Earth wasn't the Earth
When our planet was a fireball
It was raining heavily
for a thousand years
And the fireball became an ocean
That cooking water, the primal soup
A natural life-giving potion
This substance strove to find a way
To create another form of miracle
I brought a myriad atoms and
turn them into your flesh
Regenerated through destruction
and chaos
While the young world
was sculpting itself
No one could notice how you
stroke a different pose
Voracious ape who walks upright
Who deserts life to satisfy
his appetite
Don't you remember you were
the size of a bean?
Now what a shame to wear the
name of a 'human being'
Oh, here you are! Vertically standing!
He, who calls himself intelligent
But has not much for understanding
Oh, here you go, Mr. Know-it-all!
I made a mistake when I created
you long time ago
Oh, here you go
Just the mention of your name
Would make the whole world
start to shake
Who gave you right to save your life
By taking life from others?
By taking life away!
Bloodthirsty ape who walks upright
What shall I do to humble
your appetite?
Bloodthirsty ape who walks upright
What shall I do to humble
your appetite?
by RentAnAdviser.com