by RentAnAdviser.com
No more following this endless maze
Separation will define the new way
What's broken is what
leads us all astray
The chosen are renewed in amnesty
Broken, hopeless, the state
of all our fates
Revolted, woken, lead
us from this place
Nowhere to hide, strength realigned
The signal fire's alight
Given to fight, there's
hope just in sight
The signal fire's alight
Can we walk a mile in another's shoes
To determine what we have
to lose? (To lose)
Disconnection of a common reality
Becomes so lost in this
world of hypocrisy
Nowhere to hide, strength realigned
The signal fire's alight
Given to fight, there's
hope just in sight
The signal fire's alight
(Alight)
This is our one beacon
to deliver us all
To guide us away from this
decay of humanity
Nowhere to hide, strength realigned
The signal fire's alight
Given to fight, there's
hope just in sight
The signal fire's alight
(Alight)
I won't give up this fight
The signal fire is alight
by RentAnAdviser.com