by RentAnAdviser.com
Deceive me, release me, unleash me
You've unleashed the wild within
Welcome to the madness
That dwells inside these eyes
Pushed unto the breaking point
You're running out of time
This innocent blood is on your hands
Deceive me
Come face to face with the final stand
Release me
It's the part of me you
can't comprehend
Unleash me
You've unleashed the wild within
The wild within
You who spoke defiance
You who spoke in jest
The last of all my tolerance
Has left this broken man
This innocent blood is on your hands
Deceive me
Come face to face with the final stand
Release me
It's the part of me you
can't comprehend
Unleash me
You've unleashed the wild within
I remind you time and time again
You've broken the restrains
against your heart
Against the dark
Can you feel the pain of
those you've betrayed
The promises unmade, broken hearts
that fill with shame
And you're to blame
Do they call your name
There's nothing left to say,
nothing left to say
This innocent blood is on your hands
Deceive me
Come face to face with the final stand
Release me
It's the part of me you
can't comprehend
Unleash me
You've unleashed the wild within
by RentAnAdviser.com