by RentAnAdviser.com
Driving down blistered severe
The rapacious maw of our despair
Black dog follows, strip club echoes
The raven's shadow across the ghetto
Up the hill in an unmarked grave
The mother of American darkness lays
Liberty or death to start the battle
There's nonesuch place
for human chattel
Hanging by a threat
Now you can choke on it
So go and choke on it
This is a reckoning
You hear the raven's scream
Hanging by a threat
So go and choke on it
Across the devil's own half acrе
There's rusted gallows for an angеl
The ghosts that built this city scream
Of commerce and inhumanity
Cancer rides the freeway's edge
Falling statues and cigarettes
Bullets whip the screaming kettle
As tear gas cloaks the monumental
Hanging by a threat
Now you can choke on it
So go and choke on it
This is a reckoning
You hear the raven's scream
Hanging by a threat
So go and choke on it
Chained beneath a parking lot
Savaged on the auction block
In antebellum geography
Rage, horror, history
Hanging by a threat
Now you can choke on it
So go and choke on it
This is a reckoning
You hear the raven's scream
Hanging by a threat
So go and choke on it
Nevermore
by RentAnAdviser.com