The screeching halt machine
digging heels in disbelief
A bait-and-switch routine
Double-takes and double-speak
Still scripting the façade
Asphyxiate and choke the truth
All hail the money god
Repeat, echo, refrain
It's all the same
So deafening
Repeat, echo, refrain
A consequence
We asked for this
Repeat, echo, refrain
No, never again
The American scream
A coup d'état on full display,
a liar's sick charade
A traitor's grand parade
Narcissistic masquerades
for those without a say
Systematic disarray
Divide and conquer and close them in
And bury secrets deep
Make America hate again
And bleed the sheep to sleep
Repeat, echo, refrain
It's all the same
So deafening
Repeat, echo, refrain
A consequence
We asked for this
Repeat, echo, refrain
No, never again
The American scream
You try to pick the lesser of
But evil doesn't come in twos
Bellicose and balkanized
A sinking ship of fools
So kiss the hangman as you drop
The rotting corpse of decency
Just another casualty of
the American scream
Scream
Repeat, echo, refrain
It's all the same
So deafening
Repeat, echo, refrain
A consequence
We asked for this
Repeat, echo, refrain
No, never again
The American scream
Never again
by RentAnAdviser.com