by RentAnAdviser.com
I cut the weight of connection
and lead myself astray
The end will justify the means, but
in the end it stays the same
There's nothing left at all,
nothing left to see
A restrictive empty exercise
within a hollow scheme
Do you see the…
Omens? Omens
Fuck it all, ignore the omens
Omens, omens
An endless recitation thrown right
through the looking glass
I’m trapped inside a parody,
a fabricatеd past
Searching for releasе from
all this rising stress
Charted past the point of curing
with a broken compass
Motes in the eye of God,
indulging Armageddon
The devil slits the muse's throat
and drinks her last confession
Do you see the…
Omens? Omens
Fuck it all, ignore the omens
Omens, omens
I've fallen out of touch
with who you think I am
I can’t pretend to care
or bother to condemn
All this rising apathy,
it's growing every day
I can't pretend to care about
how this will end
All I see
Are omens, omens
Fuck it all, ignore the omens
I see omens, I hear omens
I say fuck it all, ignore the omens
by RentAnAdviser.com