by RentAnAdviser.com
If I can't let you go will
darkness divide?
For the fiction of love is
the truth of our lies
We were playing for keeps but
we both knew the cost
Now the only way out’s in
your heart shaped box
But I hate that it seemed
you were never enough
We were broken and bleeding
but never gave up
And I hate that I made you the enemy
And I hate that your heart
was the casualty
Now I hate that I need you
As we rest here alone
like notes on a page
The finest to compose could
not play our pain
With a candle through time I
could still see your ghost
But I can't close my eyes, for it
For it is there where you haunt
me most (Haunt me most)
Where you haunt me most
I hate that it seemed you
were never enough
We were broken and bleeding
but never gave up
And I hope that I sing
through your memory
As we echo through time in the melody
Now I hate that I need you
And I hear you now when
you said it hurt
But it had to fall, fall apart to work
As I see you now in what's left of me
Is it too late to plead insanity?
I won’t let go
'Cause I hate that it seemed
you were never enough
You were broken and bleeding
in the name of love
And I hope that we meet
in another life
I hope that we meet in another life
I don't hate that I need you
by RentAnAdviser.com