by RentAnAdviser.com
Everyone that you love is dead
Unholy ghost of Crane's delirium
Trace the fear of your silhouette
You wanted madness…. Undead Ahead
Oh how the wind it whispers
The moonlit fog ignites
With Lucifer as witness
The pumpkin rides tonight
Crimson coagulates
Severed head bouquet
Body incomplete
Sealer of your fate
Crimson calligraphy
Written on the trees
Creature from the grave, Headless
and hellbent for me
Line the streets
Murder for keeps
That's how you play trick or
treat with a heart beat
Bloody does he, bloody does he
storm through the gate way
Race the sunset, head for the bridge
You cannot kill that which has
no soul or life to take
The blood of our beloved
The Hessian comes to claim
Crimson coagulates
Severed head bouquet
Body incomplete
Sealer of your fate
Crimson calligraphy
Written on the trees
Creature from the grave, Headless
and hellbent for me
The woods, the woods
The bridge of souls too far to reach
You can't escape
Damnation on all hallows eve
This place is haunted
The woods, the woods
The bridge of souls too far to reach
You can't escape
Damnation on all hallows eve
Crimson coagulates
Severed head bouquet
Body incomplete
Sealer of your fate
Crimson calligraphy
Written on the trees
Creature from the grave, Headless
and hellbent for me
Live or die in the tale
of the midnight ride
Where reality and superstition collide
Close your eyes kiss your
dearest Katrina goodbye
And beware of the tale, tale
of the midnight ride
Revenge is cold and their
heads will roll
Menace in the moonlight
by RentAnAdviser.com