by RentAnAdviser.com
Blow the bridge to the past
Wipe the fingerprints
Melt your heart encased in wax
Steal it with a kiss
Our fate engraved
Scar enslaved
As we mutually destruct
Repose, my love, I've sinned
enough for the both of us
I'm ready to bury all of my bones
I'm ready to lie but say I won't
So tell me your secrets
And join me in pieces
To rot in this garden made of stones
Eternally yours
I feed like you taught me
and selflessly swallow
We coalesce in darkness,
so selfishly hollow
Examine the wreckage
Writhing in tempo
Invisible anguish casting a shadow
I'm ready to bury all of my bones
I'm ready to lie but say I won't
So tell me your secrets
And join me in pieces
To rot in this garden made of stones
Eternally yours
As we rest in pieces, though
I know not your name
I would suffer forever to
absolve all your pain
And in the name of love
I'm ready to bury all of my bones
I'm ready to lie but say I won't
So tell me your secrets
And join me in pieces
To rot in this garden made of stones
I'm ready to bleed to make amends
And sleep in this dirt we call our bed
So tell me your secrets
And join me in pieces
To fall and rewrite the bitter end
Eternally yours
by RentAnAdviser.com