by RentAnAdviser.com
Burn it down, brick by
brick. Made in 2006
Lost and found, losing
grip, I needed this
Question me not, for I
gave up everything.
Forget me not, cause I've not
forgotten what this means.
Strip me down, tear me apart,
you'll find one theme left.
No sign of stopping till
my veins rust.
Strip me down, Tear me apart,
you'll find one thing left.
I fucking know where I came from.
And nothing can replace
those lessons learned,
As I stood with my brothers
on the side of the road.
No longer haunted by the skeletons.
No longer haunted by the past.
For so long, it's all I've known
I'm crossing over the undertow.
For so long no one was listening
Determined to make their
deaf ears ring.
Miles repeat. My worst enemy... is me.
But then 4 soon became 6
To shatter the canvas
Handed nothing. Loss
pulling the strings
Outlived the dead trends
United by distance
For so long, it's all I've known
I'm crossing over the undertow.
For so long no one was listening
Determined to make their
deaf ears ring.
I've been to hell and back,
with no promise of return.
So I made friends with fire, to
keep from getting burned.
No money, no sleep. Dedication
10 years on the road this is sacred.
And when I'm facing a
wall, I do not quit.
...Cause if you mean it,
you will make it.
Pulled apart in a world so demanding.
I'm still here, still standing
I've sweat blood from Stockholm
to Scranton
Still here, still standing.
You can always rinse the surface,
but the stain will remain.
For so long, it's all I've known
I'm crossing over the undertow.
For so long no one was listening
I did my time.
You live, you learn,
you defy the terms,
but this house will be my home.
Beguiled, betrayed, it's
the price we pay,
as trust will be our tomb.
If you mean it, you'll make it
by RentAnAdviser.com