by RentAnAdviser.com
Get up, get up!
Fuck!
Get out, never get out, never
get out, never let go,
never let go, never go
The spiraling inside my own disguise
"This is my design"
But we're not here together
Mirror, mirror, tell me who you see
Am I you or me?
I can never remember
But you can't hide forever
I found myself by losing hope
I lost my way to find a home
I hid myself to stay alive
Now I'm ready to face my disguise
Get out, never get out, never
get out, never let go,
never let go, never go
I am locked within the box I built
From the inside out
Reassured by my doubt I (no)
I don't want this fucking (no)
codependent vice (no)
But desperate measures call
for desperate lies
Desperate lies!
I found myself by losing hope
I lost my way to find a home
I hid myself to stay alive
Now I'm ready to face my disguise
Sick of wearing a mask
Sick of hiding my face
Sick of every motherfucker
that is in my way
Sick of digging for answers
While you bury the truth
Fuck your method to my sadness,
I will bury you
Dig!
I will not become a figure
of my mistakes
I will not become the mask,
fear is not my fate
You can't turn down anger,
you can't silence pain
You will not put out the
fire that burns in me
That burns in me!
I sold my soul to my disguise
I hid myself to stay alive
I found myself by losing hope
I lost my way to find a home
I hid myself to spite my eyes
I was losing myself in my disguise
Fear I follow
Safe in sorrow
Time I borrowed
I'm ready to face my disguise
Get out, never get out, never
get out, never let go,
never let go, never go
Get out, never get out, never
get out, never let go,
never let go, never go
by RentAnAdviser.com