by RentAnAdviser.com
I felt you dragging me
into a shallow grave
The dirt became a place to
rest, but it betrays
You'll never stop me,
your reign has ended
You'll never hold down that
which has ascended
I won't run, I won't turn away
I won't let you get the best of me
I won't fall in your gravity
Open your eyes
You're the earth and I'm the sky
You are the single stone
amongst infinity
I am the wind that blows, I am
the voice inside the rain
Can you feel the cold wind blowing
Unrelenting, everlasting?
Do you feel it in your bones?
Do you feel it in your soul?
I won't run, I won't turn away
I won't let you get the best of me
I won't fall in your gravity
Open your eyes
I won't run (run), I won't turn away
I won't let you get the best of me
I won't fall (fall) in your gravity
Open your eyes
You're the earth and I'm the sky
by RentAnAdviser.com