by RentAnAdviser.com
Can't you see? I'm easily
bothered by persistence
One step from lashing out at you
You want in to get under my skin
and call yourself a friend
I've got more friends like
you, what do I do?
Is there no standard anymore?
What it takes, who I am,
where I've been, belong
You can't be something you're not
Be yourself by yourself,
stay away from me
A lesson learned in life, known
from the dawn of time
Respect, walk, what did you say?
Respect, walk, are you talking to me?
Are you talking to me?
Rock your mouth when I'm not around,
it's easy to achieve
You cry to weak friends
that sympathize
Can you hear the violins
playing your song?
Those same friends tell
me your every word
Is there no standard anymore?
What it takes, who I am,
where I've been, belong
You can't be something you're not
Be yourself by yourself,
stay away from me
A lesson learned in life, known
from the dawn of time
Respect, walk, what did you say?
Respect, walk, are you talking to me?
Are you talking to me? No way punk
Respect, walk, what did you say?
Respect, walk, are you talking to me?
Are you talking to me?
Walk on home boy
by RentAnAdviser.com