by RentAnAdviser.com
Your heart, your home, your voice,
it's got a price tag
Sign in blood, bury your
rights in a body bag
They're feeding fear through
the fault lines
You heard it here first, they got
your freedoms on the front line
Prime time, the noose at our throats
Our liberties hands run with
blood of the scapegoats
So tell me, how can we demonize
When we can't see life through
another's eyes
Pay 'em off and play 'em off
Fear rolls like a reaper through
the streets of the lost
Pay 'em off and play 'em off
But in the eyes of the storm
The truth drops like a bomb
The battle is on
Hands in chains for a
fist full of dollars
Who do we blame for the
holes in our knowledge
The past you know has been
written by the victor
So I ask you now, who is
it writing your future
The butcher, the liar, the
thief or the killer
Your freedom died quiet
in the halls of power
Starved for peace we'll eat
war until it kills us
Six feet deep with a belly
full of bullets
Pay 'em off and play 'em off
Fear rolls like a reaper through
the streets of the lost
Pay 'em off and play 'em off
But in the eyes of the storm
The truth drops like a bomb
The battle is on
The hate runs deep but
our hopes cut deeper
Now we walk through the valley
in the shadow of the reaper
Money talks, and it's
speaking in tongues
They put a price on our soul,
like they had already won
Now open wide
I see their jaws locked tight
Silent in the moment, like
prey in the floodlights
The signal is static, baptised in fire
Now we see how they talk
With a mouth full of barbed wire
Absolute power
Absolute power corrupts absolutely
Absolute power corrupts
The truth drops like a bomb
The battle is on
The truth drops like a'
Absolute power corrupts absolutely
by RentAnAdviser.com