by RentAnAdviser.com
Master of the darkness
Siren of the storm
Whisper in the silence
The king of nevermore
Keeper of the secrets
it's Reaper in the fall
Reigning here eternal, the king of nevermore
The bells will ring
Virtue extolled
Behold, destiny, thy guidance
Master of dominion, he's
the shadow on the wall
His arms are always open
He's the name we leave unspoken
He's the king of nevermore
The harbinger of all
Dark matters
Breaker of the cycle
Seeker of the soul
Shepherd in the ether
Through the gates of nevermore
Look just beyond the pale
The truth is there to
see for one and all
The answers that you seek
Lie just beyond his open door
The bells will ring
Virtue extolled
Behold, destiny, thy guidance
Master of dominion, he's
the shadow on the wall
His arms are always open
He's the name we leave unspoken
He's the king of nevermore
The harbinger of all
Dark matters
In death
In death we all sing the
hymns of nevermore
Nevermore
The promise, the constant
The requiem for every soul
Polaris inside us
We sing the hymns of nevermore
Nevermore
The harbinger of all
Dark matters
by RentAnAdviser.com