by RentAnAdviser.com
You answer to me
I am the thunder and the rain
The confusion and the pain
and when I leave I will
wash your wounds clean and leave them golden
I got the whole world swingin'
from the end of my chain
and I'm calling
I got your life in my hands and
every debt will be paid
and I'm calling
spark and the ember
You are smoke threading the wind
In time
All will return to me
All find an end
You answer to me
I am the fight and the fury
Gravity in all its glory
and when I come around I
bring the hammer of god
Down upon you
I got the whole world swingin'
from the end of my chain
and I'm calling
I got your life in my hands and
every debt will be paid
and I'm calling
Stop
Between the spark and the ember
You are smoke threading the wind
In time
All will return to me
All find an end
In time
All will return to me
You'll find no other way
You answer to me
I am the end
and the beginning
I am forever
I am eternal and nothing
stands against me
You answer to me
by RentAnAdviser.com