by RentAnAdviser.com
From crooked faith, the darkness flows
From hallowed halls, through
broken homes
To prey upon the weakest lamb
The cruelest heart is truly
Man
And when the judgment came,
they told us "turn away"
As their laughter whipped the
halls like cracking bones
Small words and hollow gestures,
the rats are closing ranks
They paint themselves as
angels, oh so wrong
Libera nos
Deliver us from the blackest of mass
Deliver us justice for the lost
Straight down
I see their wings are burning
But it's a shallow fall
Straight down
I see their wings are burning
There are no halos to be found
So save your breath
Nothing here is sacred,
nothing is divine
If heaven's gates are open, then
I think I'll wait in line
Nothing here is holy when
every faith is blind
So save your breath, I don't
need more excuses
Libera nos
Deliver us from the blackest of mass
Deliver us justice for the lost
But it's a shallow fall
It's a shallow fall
Straight down
I see their wings are burning
But it's a shallow fall
Straight down
I see their wings are burning
There are no halos to be found
I'll never see through
the eyes of your lord
But I have seen through
the eyes of a child
I'll never see through
the eyes of your lord
But I have seen through
the eyes of a child
I hope you rot
Straight down
I see their wings are burning
But it's a shallow fall
Straight down
I see their wings are burning
There are no halos to be found
From crooked faith, the darkness flows
From hallowed halls, through
broken homes
To prey upon the weakest lamb
The cruelest heart is truly
Man
by RentAnAdviser.com