by RentAnAdviser.com
I got an axe to grind, a crooked mind
You better watch your back
Starved like a vampire chasing a vein
Cruel disposition, sickness I crave
Attention, attention,
welcome to the stage
Your new sacrifice, come
sharpen your teeth
Prey, we are all prey for the sorrow
Prey, we are all prey for
the sorrow, our sorrow
Prey, prey, we're prey for the sorrow
Prey, prey, prey for the sorrow
I got an axe to grind, a crooked mind
You better watch your back
Sick validation, gut full of pills
Self-medication, it's making me ill
Attention, attention,
it's all eyes on me
I'll burn at the stake while
you ache for the kill
Prey, we are all prey for the sorrow
Prey, we are all prey for
the sorrow, our sorrow
Prey for the sorrow, (our sorrow)
Prey, prey, we're prey for the sorrow
Prey, prey, prey for the sorrow
Our new gods are empty like
the holes in our heads
We dance upon the alter
of envy and hubris
A scourge of narcissism reaps
depression in black waves
If this is your salvation,
you better pray
You better pray
One, two, three, go
Prey, we are all prey for the sorrow
Prey, we are all prey for
the sorrow, our sorrow
Prey, prey, we're prey for the sorrow
Prey, prey, prey for the sorrow
by RentAnAdviser.com