by RentAnAdviser.com
Do you see me?
Do you see what I've become
I'm not the same beast
I leave a scar on all I touch
You think you know me now
Is it better than I know myself?
I know it hurts like hell
Admitting just how you've misjudged
All my life I've been
told the same old
Don't step out, don't test the mould
We know your kind, yeah we know you
So much better than you know yourself
See, the ones that won't engage me
Are the same trying to cage me
But I can't sit still
and I won't be tame
When the lights go out
Better know your enemy
spent a lifetime shadowboxing with death
And we'll dance with the devil
'til there's no songs left
So do you see me
Do you see what I've become
I'm not the same beast, no
I leave a scar on all I touch
You think you know me now
Is it better than I know myself
I know it hurts like hell
Admitting just how you've misjudged
You don't know me, you cannot own me
The path I'm on don't fit the old me,
I bear my soul as I keep evolving
And I chase this taste for blood
See, I learned real young,
don't seek no gold
Trust no fool and you won't get sold
I never feared the dark
No, I just became it
When the lights go dead
You better pray you're safe kid
Because I've spent a lifetime
shadowboxing with death
And we'll dance with the devil
'til there's no songs left
I try
To keep my cool and not
let this hate win
I find
This mask I wear can't
keep the darkness in
The world you know was born to fade
We'll dance upon its grave
You don't know me, you cannot hold me
You should have guessed that
you can't control me
I raise my soul like a private army
and I steel myself for war
Because I leaned real young,
when you walk through hell
The devil can't buy what
you won't sell
So I took my fear, reshaped and aimed
Because when the night caves in
No one will save you
So we'll dance with the devil
'til there's no songs left
I try
To keep my cool and not
let this hate win
I find
This mask I wear can't
keep the darkness in
by RentAnAdviser.com