by RentAnAdviser.com
I spoke a vow today
And asked if god would come and play
I've dug a shallow hole
for him to sleep
But I swear he just won't answer me
I call on out is he afraid
I'll bury him down with
the ones he keeps
And if the devil's listening
I'll come for him as well
If I suspect he had a hand to play
And if I see his face in town
There's room for two down underground
Nothing's gonna stop me 'til I'm done
Until I'm done
Because tonight I'm killing gods
Killing gods
It's guilt and frustration,
it's everything between
The silence and the absence
hitting home
Peripheral glances and the
chasing of a sound
I never knew I'd miss until it's gone
So ask me how I'm coping
And I'll smile and tell
you "I'm just fine"
While down inside I'm drowning
in the fucking rain
Because when everything is empty
And your heart is set to cave
Sometimes all you wish for
Is a place, is a place
to place the blame
Burn your heaven
Flood your hell
Drown you in your wishing wells
Burn your heaven
Flood your hell
Damn you all
Because tonight I'm killing gods
The incendiary shock wave,
scorched earth policy
The devastation that only
loss will leave
The chants and incantations
of daily rituals
A subtle lapse in brutal honesty
So ask me how I'm coping
And I'll smile and tell
you "I'm just fine"
While down inside I'm screaming
'til I fucking bleed
Because when everyone's expendable
And your heart can't take the wait
The last thing that you wish for
Is the face, is the face
to face the pain
Burn your heaven
Flood your hell
Drown you in your wishing wells
Burn your heaven
Flood your hell
Damn you all
Because tonight I'm killing gods
I spoke a vow today
And asked if god would come and play
'Cause I just want to
cut that fucker down
Face me
None survive
The devil and god have died inside me
by RentAnAdviser.com