by RentAnAdviser.com
Read all about it if you want to know
Read all about what they
want you to know
Everything is god online, and
it's as evil as it gets
This is not a fuckin' trick, either
follow or repent (No choice)
Get infected by a vertical event
Check the meter, check your watch
Are they ever gonna stop?
Runnin' out of daylight,
nighttime's better
But we know how to handle
the truth, motherfucker
Scandalous know-it-all,
feedback chamber
Nobody wants the proof,
they want a number
We don't deny what is
wrong with our lives
We can't decide what is left of our
right to silence our remains
Buried in the back and
I'm sick and alive
Hollow as a breath, the
further you dive
Oh, how I missed your honesty
You never miss with your intensity
You're gonna need a new disguise
Vessels burst, veins release
Just slide into the nearest lie
(One, two, oh my god)
All the ligatures are getting
tight, like a style
Murder another mouth before the trial
Scalpel and then you scalp
'em to fucking death
Kills for the other vampires
and surrogates
It's a ploy for attention and evidence
All your fucking monsters are
flaws in your common sense
Do the dance while the shovels
are breaking dirt
Everybody mind your fuckin'
business or you get hurt
We don't deny what is
wrong with our lives
We can't decide what is left of our
right to silence our remains
Buried in the back and
I'm sick and alive
Hollow as a breath, the
further you dive
Oh, how I missed your namaste
You never miss with your integrity
You're gonna need a new disguise
Vessels burst, veins release
Just slide into the nearest lie
Read all about it if you want to know
(Everything is god online)
Stoned like a beast on
a chain lookin' dead
Feelin' strange, what the fuck
I'm material to sew into the stains
Like a catalogue of pain, like
a martyr in restraints
I can kill with a will, and
it's stronger every day
I'm a knife, I'm a gun,
I'm a slit, I'm a scar
I'm a scream, I'm a death,
I'm a threat, I'm afraid
That you will never understand
I'm not the same
You better call the triple
9, I want a face
That you can only recognize
I'm afraid, I'm afraid,
I'm afraid, I'm afraid
When everything is god
online, nothing is
by RentAnAdviser.com