by RentAnAdviser.com
What a world, the horizon's
Coming like a hell-bent
killing machine
Can't afford to be the
goddamn wreckage
Burn it all again at a million degrees
Calling all the adamant upper-level
Undefeated counterfeit cunts
with a reason to fear
Throw away all the meaningless
shit that's clinging
The enemy is here, I said stop
Give it to three
I'm gonna show you how to do
it if you know what I mean
One by one against, give me the name
All you shiny pretty never-
wills ruined the game
You hold all the keys, so the
chains shouldn't hold you
I know you heard me,
I fucking told you
Old does not mean dead,
new does not mean best
No hard feelings, I'm tired of being
right about everything I've said
Yours does not mean mine,
kill does not mean die
We are not your kind
No excuses, I challenge you
to all out fucking life
Drop that shit and put
it on a pedestal
Children are afraid of the gods
Raise your hands and show
me what's impossible
That makes us even, never
tell me the odds
What a bore, I'm getting
stuck in a metaphor
I don't wanna go to sleep
I need a breakdown quick
in negotiations
Get it all together and remember
to seethe, stop
Give it to three
I'm gonna show you how to do
it if you know what I mean
Drive by violence, more of the same
I can see where you're going,
and I'm really ashamed
Do you think when you act or just
act like you're thinking?
I gotta know now, you better tell me
Old does not mean dead,
new does not mean best
No hard feelings, I'm tired of being
right about everything I've said
Yours does not mean mine,
kill does not mean die
We are not your kind
I challenge you to all out life
We are gathered here today
to get it right
Repeat after me:
"I will not celebrate mediocrity
I will not worship empty shells
I will not listen to worthless noises
I will not subject myself to selected
predictable choices
My time, my attention
My quality should not
be bought and sold
For convenience's sake, ever"
We are not your kind
Old does not mean dead,
new does not mean best
No hard feelings, I'm tired of being
right about everything I've said
Yours does not mean mine,
kill does not mean die
Pay attention, it's gonna be a while
'til I really feel alright
Old does not mean dead,
new does not mean best
No hard feelings, I'm tired of being
right about everything I've said
Yours does not mean mine,
kill does not mean die
We are not your kind
No excuses, I challenge you
to all out fucking life
All out life, yeah
I challenge you to all out
fucking life, yeah
Live, live, live, life
by RentAnAdviser.com