Holding you down, down by your throat.
Just enough to keep your fucking mouth shut.
Can't stand to hear you scream God.
Because he's not fucking here bitch.
And how does it feel now?
1 - OK
Don't worry you're not another rape victim.
It's just me destroying your beauty.
And how does it feel now?
2 - OK
How does it feel now?
3 - OK
That I'm ripping out all of the fake pieces in your face
4 - OK
And what will you do now,
once all of your beautiful skin,
Is in my pockets?
5 - OK
What cosmetic will fix this mess?
6 - OK
Fix this mess
7 - OK
8 - OK
That is now your face?
9 - OK
Was this all worth it?
10 - OK
For your fake fucking beauty
11 - OK
Was this all worth it?
12 - OK
For your fake fucking beauty
13 - OK
The price of beauty was more than you thought.
The price of beauty was more than you thought
14 - OK
How does it feel now?
15 - OK
16 - OK
The price
17 - OK
18 - OK
Was more than you thought