by RentAnAdviser.com
One day there will be no more pain like an opiate wonderland
No more worry, it will all just end
And all our forward movement will finally cease
The human machine will finally bleed,
The human machine will finally cease to be
So set yourself free,
and disengage from reality
And disengage from reality
The grounds will shake and your children will tremble,
Soon enough the machine will fall
And we will all crumble,
The human machine will finally bleed and cease to be
We'll finally be set free, be set free, be set free
Just be glad you know what life is,
Be glad you know
You know what life is!
One day there will be no worry,
No more pain, it will all just end
And all our forward movement will finally cease
Disengage