Genocide!
1 - OK
2 - OK
We've been beating cheeks for the better part of our existence.
Constantly spreading disease of our humanity
3 - OK
Rotting her out!
4 - OK
We've been fucking this whore.
Mother Earth for awhile
5 - OK
She's a filthy bitch anyway
6 - OK
We've been fucking this whore.
Mother Earth for awhile
7 - OK
She's a filthy bitch anyway
8 - OK
Rotting her from the inside
9 - OK
Penetrating deeper and deeper every day. We are at our end.
So let's continue to move forward and destroy ourselves
10 - OK
Rotting her out!
11 - OK
Rotting her out! Genocide of all humanity
12 - OK
Genocide of your reality
13 - OK
Genocide of all humanity
14 - OK
Genocide of your reality
15 - OK
Genocide!