Push your care, push your burdens aside,
erase everything inside and leave just one thing on your mind
1 - OK
You only live once so just go fucking nuts, go!
2 - OK
Live life hard
3 - OK
You only get one shot, so shoot! With every breath you take, you're dying
4 - OK
With every step we take, we're falling apart,
if we only had one chance, we'd breathe
5 - OK
Let's take the chance right now and scream
6 - OK
You only live one life
7 - OK
For a very short time, so make every second divine. Go!
8 - OK
Live life hard, live life hard
9 - OK
Are you still breathing? It's your heart that's beating inside
That keeps us alive and for the very first time
10 - OK
We're pushing aside to surrender, everything that I see in my eyes
11 - OK
Except for the one thing on my mind, that I am alive
12 - OK
For the very first time, for the first time
13 - OK
Pushing worry aside
14 - OK
For the first time
15 - OK
Pushing worry aside
16 - OK
Erase everything inside
17 - OK
18 - OK
Live life hard, live life hard, live life hard, live life hard