How much must I curse your name
1 - OK
And put your beliefs to shame
Before you prove yourself
2 - OK
And end this life?
End this life
3 - OK
And I'll say a fucking prayer
4 - OK
Because I know it won't be answered
5 - OK
Where is your god?
6 - OK
7 - OK
Where is your fucking god?
8 - OK
And even though I don't believe in you.
I pray for the day.
That you end this life
9 - OK
So please take me away
10 - OK
I want the hand of god to come and strike me down
11 - OK
I want the hand of god to come and strike me down.
Where is your god?
12 - OK
13 - OK
Where is your fucking god?
14 - OK
For all the prayers that go unanswered
15 - OK
16 - OK
Why do you think that is?
17 - OK
For the families that waste their time
18 - OK
Open your eyes and all your prayers will go unanswered
19 - OK
Why do you think that is?
20 - OK
For the families that waste their time
21 - OK
Open your fucking eyes