by RentAnAdviser.com
Don't keep on telling me that
I'm gonna pull through
When you don't know low like I do
I'm afraid of the things I don't say
The thoughts in my head that keep
me tossing, turning, lying awake
Don't keep on telling me that
I'm gonna pull through
When you don't know low like I do
I've been running away again
Chasing after all the battles
I can never win
I don't think that I can
take much more it
It feels like I've lost
it all (Lost it all)
Who will save me when
I can't save myself?
Hard to think we were born
to live this way
Burning bridges, ripping stitches
out to drown the pain
Bleed me out, run me dry,
watch the hammer fall
Let the river run and bury
me beneath it all
Bury me
Bury me beneath it all
I've been running away again
Chasing after all the battles
I can never win
I don't think that I can
take much more it
It feels like I've lost
it all (Lost it all)
Who will save me when
I can't save myself?
Searching for answers
A cure for this cancer
It's all in my head
I'm one step from the edge
I've been running away again
Chasing after all the battles
I can never win
I don't think that I can
take much more it
It feels like I've lost it all
I've been running away again
Chasing after all the battles
I can never win
I don't think that I can
take much more it
It feels like I've lost
it all (Lost it all)
Who will save me when
I can't save myself?
by RentAnAdviser.com