by RentAnAdviser.com
I buried the judgment
I covered my tracks
Soon to be forgotten
There's a new life ahead
It was my hope that was fading
I was caught in a trap
It's the burden of failure
I carried on my back
Let's get this straight
A lot has changed in the last year
Thought I had everything together
But watched it all disappear
I put my faith in the wrong things
When I woke up, it was
gone, I gave up on me
Didn't even recognize myself
Self worth is not found
in someone else
Chase what you want, never give up
Salt the wound, all ties are cut
Now I see
I was broken to be made a better me
Had to learn to let it
go and let it be
Sometimes we're too blind to see
The hardest lessons that we learn
Are the ones where knowledge
must be earned
It's what makes us human
It's what gets us through it
Weighed down by the pressures
of saving face
This is a dark world,
I'll be your witness
Witness
Now I see
I was broken to be made a better me
Had to learn to let it
go and let it be
Sometimes we're too blind to see
Learn to let it go and let it be
Learn to let it go
by RentAnAdviser.com