They appear. I remember when the fire was security, now it's killing me.
A wolf can't hunt without its prey, so take me to my grave. The
1 - OK
Demons dance by the fireside,
but tonight they migrate to my bedside
2 - OK
Burn the bed, burn everything
It's a lie anyway
3 - OK
There's nowhere left to run
There's nowhere left for me to be
4 - OK
Without you by my side
5 - OK
I cry but if you take a closer look
you'll see it's a demon's eyes
6 - OK
There's no coming back for me
For my spirit guide is trapped inside my brain
7 - OK
I don't know who I am.
In the name of the Father and the Holy Ghost.
Close your gates, lock the doors, there is no hope
8 - OK
Burn the bed, burn everything
It's a lie anyway
9 - OK
There's nowhere left to run
10 - OK
There's nowhere left for me to be.
Without you by my side
11 - OK
How could the world take you from me
12 - OK
They all deserve to burn with me
13 - OK
Burn the bed, burn everything.
It's a lie anyway
14 - OK
There's nowhere left to run, there's nowhere left for me to be.
Without you by my side
15 - OK
How could the world take you from me?
16 - OK
They all deserve to burn with me