Raping her and hacking, slashing, violated.
Raping her and hacking, slashing, violated
1 - OK
I'm not sorry, I don't care at all for what I did.
You deserve everything you get
2 - OK
Disinclined, her fear is keeping me enticed.
Her gateway of sin exposed for fornication.
Get over your dysphasia!
I see the moisture in your eyes is dehydrating!
Your screaming vibrations!
Only draw me nigh to rupturing climax!
As she chokes and gargles spit
3 - OK
I stimulate her salty clitoris.
Get over your dysphasia!
I see the moisture in your eyes is dehydrating!
Your screaming vibrations!
Only draw me nigh to rupturing climax!
4 - OK
Cutting incisions while reaching climax.
How can you expect me to let up?
You deserve it, give me your tongue!
I want to leave you an eternal taste of me.
Let them know in hell
5 - OK
Why fight?! You'll just rue the day!
That you try to escape the conscience of the dead
6 - OK
Hold your throat and pray for help.
Take this oath to the grave and never let it out.
Look in these eyes and endure the sleep you'll need!
Before you awake.
7 - OK
Fucked and left for dead
8 - OK
This is war, fight!
I am bored, but fulfilled
9 - OK
Please, if you don't mind, fulfill my passion
10 - OK
Gagging on my semen is required!
Swallow, spread it on your face.
Choke on the snot and reingest all of the foam.
Take one final breath.
11 - OK
I want to see what you have learned
12 - OK
And what you stand for.
Choking and dry heaving.