The devil is dead.
I have never felt the way that I have, until I left the valley in flames.
Let it burn, let it die, blind the all-seeing eye, but I know smoke will never clear in hell
1 - OK
The smell of burning oak makes me sick.
Still, I breathe deep
2 - OK
Still, I cross to the other side
3 - OK
But I hear a voice behind me say
4 - OK
I, the еye closed its final time as I had walkеd through the flames. Will
5 - OK
Will, the will of a beast is nothing compared to the will of a god
6 - OK
I'll find, I'll find my peace when the bones of the devil lay at my feet.
You, you and I are one, mark my words, I will find you
7 - OK
I will find you
8 - OK
A beast will always smell the blood of a coward and a narrow-minded fool will always follow down the narrow path to the blade that can make a god bleed
9 - OK
Still, you are weak.
You're just a boy with his mother's eyes
10 - OK
That carries the weight of his father's heart
11 - OK
I always feel like there's something that I've left behind
12 - OK
It's me, it's me
13 - OK
Until you realize who I am
14 - OK
I'll find my peace when the bones of the devil lay at my feet.
You, you and I are one, mark my words, I will find you!